#### LEVI EMERSON ARNETT

### 204 S Walnut Cooksville Illinois, 61730

619-750-2154 • larnett.br@outlook.com

#### **Professional Summary:**

I am a hardworking student veteran with an enthusiastic interest in computers and technology. I am currently working on my associates in computer science with the intention to transfer to a 4 year university. I have worked in many different organizations such as government, startup, corporate and education. My interests include: operating systems, cybersecurity, virtualization, international relations and philosophy.

#### **Technical Skills:**

- Software Active Directory, Docker, Mobileiron, Salesforce, Snap VMware, VirtualBox, Widows Deployment Toolkit.
- Operating Systems Windows 7/10, MacOS, iOS, Linux (Arch, CentOS, Kali, Manjaro, Ubuntu).
- 1 year of scripting and automation of system administration tasks.
- 4 years experience end user help desk support, troubleshooting and documentation of procedures.
- 4 years of experience in computer repair, maintenance, assembly, configuration of different environments.
- 5 years of experience in a highly technical and professional office environment.
- 5 years of professional writing, public speaking and presentation.

#### **Professional Experience:**

Account Manager Tradesmen International Bloomington, IL June 2017 - October 2017

- Managed a brand new sales territory spanning the entirety of Central Illinois with the
  expectation to create and grow sales while establishing a footing in the area among several
  other competitors.
- Created strong client relationships as a labor consultant helping clients grow their business while maintaining a timeline and staying under budget.
- Built strong relationships and camaraderie with Field Employees providing them with a safe working environment and ensuring they stayed gainfully employed.
- Performed administrative functions critical to HR and sales

## IT Mobile Device Analyst Country Financial Bloomington, IL February 2017-June 2017

- Provided highly technical tier III level customer support to users over the phone, with digital correspondence or in person.
- Trained users on new features and updates made to existing technology.
- Helped create documentation and implement new corporate procedures as new technology and updates were made.
- Auditing of inventory, users, and testing profiles using company device management Platform MobileIron.
- Corresponded and assisted service providers such as; Verizon, AT&T and Apple.
- Tracking and ordering of new inventory as company mobile devices progressed throughout their deployment lifecycle.
- Managed shipping and receiving for the deployment of new devices using the UPS Campus ship platform.

# IT Support Analyst Dealstruck Inc. Carlsbad, CA November 2015-November 2016

- Triaged "Tech Help" tickets submitted by end users and contractors through the Salesforce CRM platform routing them to appropriate internal and external resources.
- Installed, modified, and repaired computer hardware and software while managing all company-wide routine troubleshooting and maintenance of Windows 7/10 laptops and desktops.
- Created new company users, pushed security permissions using Active Directory and Google Suite.
- Resolved technical problems with Local Area Networks (LAN), Wide Area Networks (WAN), and other systems.
- Built and established an inventory database and tracked all company IT assets.
- Assisted in the establishment of IT procedures for, but not limited to, employee on-boarding, off-boarding, computer hardware requests, software installation.
- Interfaced with IT support contractors for escalated IT issues and routine maintenance.
- Documented all IT and Admin procedures and troubleshooting steps on the internal corporate wiki.
- Built reports on daily, weekly, and monthly metrics of performance for assisting end users with tickets submitted using the Salesforce CRM platform.
- Took on additional role as an administrator of the VOIP Phone system used by sales, creating new users and building new dialer lists and phone groups.
- Worked with vendors to provision additional hardware and IT assets at the direction of the CTO.

## Intelligence Analyst United States Marine Corps. Okinawa, Japan July 2011 – October 2015

- Conceptualized, drafted, created and presented daily Top Secret level intelligence briefs to commanding staff leaders of the top echelon of military leadership.
- Led a team of half a dozen intelligence specialists to inspect, analyze and interpret worldwide satellite imagery to help provide situational awareness for real-time operations for US forces in hostile territory.
- Provided support to help desk functions related to troubleshooting of Top Secret Networks and all connected machines.
- Trained biannually on standard methods and procedures for Cyber Security operations.
- Closely worked with foreign nations in the planning and execution of military exercises involving thousands of active duty military personnel.
- Coordinated the operations of a small security detachment as the chief bodyguard of the Commanding General of the Third Marine Expeditionary Force while ensuring the General's safety during international travel.
- Served as the unit's Training Non-Commissioned Officer, responsible for the safe keeping of over 400 military personnel's records, and ensured that they were trained to Marine Corps standards of education and readiness as dictated by Department of Defense guidelines and instructions.

#### **Education**

- Blue Ridge High School, August 2007-May 2011
- Navy and Marine Corps Intelligence School, November 2011-April 2012
- University of Maryland University College (Non Degree Seeking Sociology Classes) January 2014-December 2014
- OSHA 10 Cert
- Heartland Community College, A.S. Computer Science (Current)